fragrance time people
so got another package and we are going
to see what we got I kind of like the
idea of opening the packages from
scratch so we can be surprised together
now you can look behind me got my little
perfume collection growing she getting
there she's still a baby but she coming
Al okay okay so what do we have today
everybody
peanuts some these I need these peanuts
I got to ship something so we not going
to get rid of those
but here it is look at her come on out
Lucy oh my
gosh you know what I give y'all 10 out
of 10 out of 10 out of 10 on your
packaging that's what got us over here
in this country we so used to this
little woo woo woo woo packaging it
ain't saying nothing to us a little
regular box with nothing going
on y'all over here
L y'all making us fall in love with you
just because of the packages and some of
us are our grandparents we will keep
this box just like a Crown Royale bag
honey we will come up with everything to
do or those butter cookie
tins we got them all over holding stuff
okay we're back on track
here it is oh oh it's not just a sticker
y'all has texture oh this is
nice okay let's see what it's given
let's open the box
together
oh I see you booy boo I see
you here she is
y'all can I smell it already
y'all know I be so skeptical I can smell
it already how you smell it and you a't
even open it I can smell it already I
can't okay
so
okay here we go
people here we
go I'm ready let's use this post point
cuz I don't have anything on that today
I didn't put on no perfume today so
perfect opportunity
wow I'm not good with notes some of
y'all are so good at that that's not my
calling that's not
my it's settling
in it's starting
to feel like a woman that's what this is
doing
feeling it loing it yeah go and get it
there's no reason not to checking the
details there's no reason not to buy
this go ahead and get it it's too late
for Christmas you should have thought of
that sooner but it is not too late for
any day just because you feel like it
all right
so I don't even want to mess up the name
I know some people be trying I'm not
going to try you just look at that link
down there here and you can get the name
because uh fakar LFA that's what I think
it says and um that's all I know the
rest I don't know what that means and
yes
authentical you hear that that's how you
going to know all right everybody check
out that link down there and if that
link is not on my Tik Tok video or
wherever this video ends up it may end
up on YouTube you can always check my
Amazon store that link is out there here
and you can still get this product but
start with a Tik Tok link okay
o why are you in my face like this this
is ridiculous oh my gosh oh